{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947507981508","data":{"timestamp":" 947507981508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_r_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947507988178","data":{"timestamp":" 947507988178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_y_d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947507994814","data":{"timestamp":" 947507994814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508001500","data":{"timestamp":" 947508001500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508008135","data":{"timestamp":" 947508008135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_h_m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508014786","data":{"timestamp":" 947508014786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_h_v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508021421","data":{"timestamp":" 947508021420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508028093","data":{"timestamp":" 947508028092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_e_s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508034743","data":{"timestamp":" 947508034743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508036136","data":{"timestamp":" 947508036135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8342a8ff-5945-4b53-a487-f420840709f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508070543","data":{"timestamp":" 947508070542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508077189","data":{"timestamp":" 947508077188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508083840","data":{"timestamp":" 947508083838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508091321","data":{"timestamp":" 947508091320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508097997","data":{"timestamp":" 947508097997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_z_s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508104631","data":{"timestamp":" 947508104631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_k_p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508111271","data":{"timestamp":" 947508111271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508117924","data":{"timestamp":" 947508117924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_e_s"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508124568","data":{"timestamp":" 947508124567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_h_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508131168","data":{"timestamp":" 947508131168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508137823","data":{"timestamp":" 947508137823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_a_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508148633","data":{"timestamp":" 947508148632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_k_p"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508155238","data":{"timestamp":" 947508155238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_g_l"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508161869","data":{"timestamp":" 947508161869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_h_m"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508168531","data":{"timestamp":" 947508168530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_z"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508175182","data":{"timestamp":" 947508175182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_a_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508181826","data":{"timestamp":" 947508181826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_z_s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508189322","data":{"timestamp":" 947508189321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_z_s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508195955","data":{"timestamp":" 947508195955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_r_z"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508202610","data":{"timestamp":" 947508202609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_l_b"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508209228","data":{"timestamp":" 947508209228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_h_ch"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508215837","data":{"timestamp":" 947508215837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_f_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508226690","data":{"timestamp":" 947508226689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508233360","data":{"timestamp":" 947508233360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_ch_y"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508240013","data":{"timestamp":" 947508240012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_y_d"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508246685","data":{"timestamp":" 947508246685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508254536","data":{"timestamp":" 947508254535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 74bf3b9f-a219-4090-bcb5-13d5e2d5444d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508278318","data":{"timestamp":" 947508278318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_k_p"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508285026","data":{"timestamp":" 947508285026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508291660","data":{"timestamp":" 947508291660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508298330","data":{"timestamp":" 947508298330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508304944","data":{"timestamp":" 947508304943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508311579","data":{"timestamp":" 947508311579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508318260","data":{"timestamp":" 947508318260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_p_v"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508324919","data":{"timestamp":" 947508324918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_y_d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508331589","data":{"timestamp":" 947508331589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_i_w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508338244","data":{"timestamp":" 947508338244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_g_t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508349079","data":{"timestamp":" 947508349079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_h_m"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508355714","data":{"timestamp":" 947508355714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_g_t"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508362357","data":{"timestamp":" 947508362356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_i_w"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508369022","data":{"timestamp":" 947508369022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_z"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508375692","data":{"timestamp":" 947508375692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_a_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508382345","data":{"timestamp":" 947508382345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_ch_y"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508388987","data":{"timestamp":" 947508388986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508395643","data":{"timestamp":" 947508395643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_p_v"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508402296","data":{"timestamp":" 947508402296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_h_ch"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508408959","data":{"timestamp":" 947508408959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_f_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508419799","data":{"timestamp":" 947508419799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508426443","data":{"timestamp":" 947508426443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_w"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508433880","data":{"timestamp":" 947508433880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_w"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508440537","data":{"timestamp":" 947508440537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_y_d"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508447190","data":{"timestamp":" 947508447190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508455038","data":{"timestamp":" 947508455038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" da406796-1ff3-4187-8456-5f6191ea00f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_z_s_d"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508476216","data":{"timestamp":" 947508476216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508480068","data":{"timestamp":" 947508480068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508485485","data":{"timestamp":" 947508485485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508491076","data":{"timestamp":" 947508491076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508503237","data":{"timestamp":" 947508503237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508508969","data":{"timestamp":" 947508508969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508512890","data":{"timestamp":" 947508512890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-r-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508517023","data":{"timestamp":" 947508517023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508520892","data":{"timestamp":" 947508520891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508538660","data":{"timestamp":" 947508538660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" cfd8f501-23a6-4932-9c96-b1d36d8f716d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508567977","data":{"timestamp":" 947508567976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_ch_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508574579","data":{"timestamp":" 947508574579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_p_v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508582138","data":{"timestamp":" 947508582138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_p_v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508592231","data":{"timestamp":" 947508592231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_p_v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508598836","data":{"timestamp":" 947508598835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508599764","data":{"timestamp":" 947508599763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508617231","data":{"timestamp":" 947508617231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508633209","data":{"timestamp":" 947508633209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 7900c518-b83c-448d-80b2-4843cfc13e67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508650556","data":{"timestamp":" 947508650556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508654907","data":{"timestamp":" 947508654907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_t-i-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508660715","data":{"timestamp":" 947508660715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_t-i-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508665186","data":{"timestamp":" 947508665186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-y-j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508672052","data":{"timestamp":" 947508672052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_o-b-l"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508676244","data":{"timestamp":" 947508676244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-y-h"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508680640","data":{"timestamp":" 947508680640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-y-w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508686407","data":{"timestamp":" 947508686407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-z-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508690148","data":{"timestamp":" 947508690148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_y-m-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508695584","data":{"timestamp":" 947508695584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-y"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508701988","data":{"timestamp":" 947508701988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508709118","data":{"timestamp":" 947508709118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508714613","data":{"timestamp":" 947508714613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-a-d"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508719479","data":{"timestamp":" 947508719479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508719528","data":{"timestamp":" 947508719528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508734724","data":{"timestamp":" 947508734723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508750657","data":{"timestamp":" 947508750657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6ae96b8-4b78-42a0-a467-8453203704f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508769896","data":{"timestamp":" 947508769895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508770290","data":{"timestamp":" 947508770289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508770534","data":{"timestamp":" 947508770534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508770867","data":{"timestamp":" 947508770867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508771111","data":{"timestamp":" 947508771110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508774585","data":{"timestamp":" 947508774584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508774888","data":{"timestamp":" 947508774887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508775808","data":{"timestamp":" 947508775807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508776238","data":{"timestamp":" 947508776238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508779198","data":{"timestamp":" 947508779198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508779489","data":{"timestamp":" 947508779489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508780346","data":{"timestamp":" 947508780345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508781024","data":{"timestamp":" 947508781023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508781772","data":{"timestamp":" 947508781771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508782112","data":{"timestamp":" 947508782111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508782399","data":{"timestamp":" 947508782398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508782727","data":{"timestamp":" 947508782727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508783003","data":{"timestamp":" 947508783002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508786724","data":{"timestamp":" 947508786724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508787117","data":{"timestamp":" 947508787117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508787370","data":{"timestamp":" 947508787369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508787694","data":{"timestamp":" 947508787694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508787938","data":{"timestamp":" 947508787938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508791460","data":{"timestamp":" 947508791459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508791763","data":{"timestamp":" 947508791763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508792680","data":{"timestamp":" 947508792679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508793116","data":{"timestamp":" 947508793116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508796069","data":{"timestamp":" 947508796068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508796362","data":{"timestamp":" 947508796362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508797217","data":{"timestamp":" 947508797216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508797900","data":{"timestamp":" 947508797900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508798647","data":{"timestamp":" 947508798647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508798983","data":{"timestamp":" 947508798982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508799271","data":{"timestamp":" 947508799270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508799598","data":{"timestamp":" 947508799598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508799874","data":{"timestamp":" 947508799873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508803311","data":{"timestamp":" 947508803310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508803450","data":{"timestamp":" 947508803449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 93a77583-7e24-49a1-8ebc-e52be6533e90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508818590","data":{"timestamp":" 947508818590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mla-za-ba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508825618","data":{"timestamp":" 947508825618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ng'o-mta-ba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508831250","data":{"timestamp":" 947508831249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mta-mke-ba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508836115","data":{"timestamp":" 947508836115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_yi-nge-ba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508841670","data":{"timestamp":" 947508841670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_go-ba-mku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508846442","data":{"timestamp":" 947508846442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ba-ki-ng'i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508851578","data":{"timestamp":" 947508851578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_nja-msta-ba"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508857031","data":{"timestamp":" 947508857031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mna-ba-he"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508862296","data":{"timestamp":" 947508862296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ku-do-ba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508867502","data":{"timestamp":" 947508867502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mle-ba-he"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" mle"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508874556","data":{"timestamp":" 947508874556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mle-ba-he"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508880354","data":{"timestamp":" 947508880353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" a976b356-85c7-4d82-96a5-a685f19d8bd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mle-ba-he"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508899612","data":{"timestamp":" 947508899612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mza-ha-ba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508904126","data":{"timestamp":" 947508904126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mla-mcha-ba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508909451","data":{"timestamp":" 947508909451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mka-ng'a-ba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508917918","data":{"timestamp":" 947508917918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_da-ba-ja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508923945","data":{"timestamp":" 947508923945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_da-ba-ja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508930785","data":{"timestamp":" 947508930785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_pa-ta-ba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508936163","data":{"timestamp":" 947508936163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_dha-ba-mta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508941885","data":{"timestamp":" 947508941884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_da-ba-ta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508947506","data":{"timestamp":" 947508947506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_da-ba-ta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508952958","data":{"timestamp":" 947508952958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ra-ba-ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508958801","data":{"timestamp":" 947508958801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mba-mja-ba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508963749","data":{"timestamp":" 947508963749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_nya-ba-ga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508969534","data":{"timestamp":" 947508969532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 8e835cde-5000-4970-8778-6b512aa70127"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_nya-ba-ga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508990995","data":{"timestamp":" 947508990994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_zi-ka-ba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947508995877","data":{"timestamp":" 947508995877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mte-ki-ba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509001216","data":{"timestamp":" 947509001215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ngu-di-ba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509006829","data":{"timestamp":" 947509006828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ba-mbu-nde"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509013260","data":{"timestamp":" 947509013260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ba-nye-twa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509025981","data":{"timestamp":" 947509025980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mko-ba-mvu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509031508","data":{"timestamp":" 947509031507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_mko-ba-mvu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509036635","data":{"timestamp":" 947509036635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ba-nde-yi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509041558","data":{"timestamp":" 947509041558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ba-mfa-mku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509047412","data":{"timestamp":" 947509047412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_lu-ba-mfa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" lu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509052761","data":{"timestamp":" 947509052761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_lu-ba-mfa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509058680","data":{"timestamp":" 947509058680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ndu-mfa-ba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509064471","data":{"timestamp":" 947509064470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 319687f7-e6cb-4f7b-b466-58238abc71cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ba..ba.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ba_ndu-mfa-ba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509087062","data":{"timestamp":" 947509087062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6c96eea-f15f-4139-8089-63c8aec19fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fi_ba_ko"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509093720","data":{"timestamp":" 947509093720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6c96eea-f15f-4139-8089-63c8aec19fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwo_mju_ba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509100390","data":{"timestamp":" 947509100389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6c96eea-f15f-4139-8089-63c8aec19fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwo_ba_mlu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509107033","data":{"timestamp":" 947509107033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6c96eea-f15f-4139-8089-63c8aec19fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ba_mfu_mjo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509108641","data":{"timestamp":" 947509108641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" e6c96eea-f15f-4139-8089-63c8aec19fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ba..ba.noShow..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_ba_mfu_mjo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509127549","data":{"timestamp":" 947509127548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BA"," userResponse":" BA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509128623","data":{"timestamp":" 947509128622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BA"," userResponse":" BA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509131966","data":{"timestamp":" 947509131965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" be"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BE"," userResponse":" BE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509133031","data":{"timestamp":" 947509133030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" be"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BE"," userResponse":" BE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509138920","data":{"timestamp":" 947509138919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509139999","data":{"timestamp":" 947509139998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509143858","data":{"timestamp":" 947509143857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BO"," userResponse":" BO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509144934","data":{"timestamp":" 947509144933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BO"," userResponse":" BO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509151917","data":{"timestamp":" 947509151916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" BU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509152989","data":{"timestamp":" 947509152988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" BU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509156549","data":{"timestamp":" 947509156547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509156644","data":{"timestamp":" 947509156643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 889f5f00-17bb-4bed-b47e-500a18ba0c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" BU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509177060","data":{"timestamp":" 947509177060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509182909","data":{"timestamp":" 947509182909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509187630","data":{"timestamp":" 947509187630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509192810","data":{"timestamp":" 947509192810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509198492","data":{"timestamp":" 947509198491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509203445","data":{"timestamp":" 947509203445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509207985","data":{"timestamp":" 947509207985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509212801","data":{"timestamp":" 947509212801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509220477","data":{"timestamp":" 947509220477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509230984","data":{"timestamp":" 947509230984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509236678","data":{"timestamp":" 947509236678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509241841","data":{"timestamp":" 947509241841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509247621","data":{"timestamp":" 947509247619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_153915"," gameId":" 995710e5-f5b8-457d-ad62-407de3f49a01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}